<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>public opinion on Sun Yufei</title>
    <link>/categories/public-opinion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in public opinion on Sun Yufei</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2023</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/public-opinion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Political Communication</title>
      <link>/project/political_communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/political_communication/</guid>
      <description>People do not merely respond to the outside world; they recognize, process, and make choices. I am interested in how this psychological process is achieved within media interactions among the sender, carrier, and receiver. This also makes my research different from the prevalent political-communication studies that focus on the content and means of the media. Instead, I focus more on how people respond to them, for instance, what the audience actually feels, understands, and does when they are exposed to a political message from the government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democracy in Modern China</title>
      <link>/project/democracy_in_modern_china/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/democracy_in_modern_china/</guid>
      <description>Socioeconomic inequality includes systematic discrepancies among citizens in income, assets, mobility, accessible resources, etc. I am interested in this structural property&amp;rsquo;s effects, paths, and mechanisms on individual and group political decisions and behaviors. In particular, how do people recognize inequality (what aspects of inequality)? How does their awareness and understanding of inequality affect their political cognition, preferences, and decisions? Even more interestingly, what (or&amp;hellip;who) forms the masses&amp;rsquo; inequality perceptions?
For more imformation, Please visit the project page</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
