<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Sun Yufei</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Sun Yufei</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2023</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Political Communication</title>
      <link>/project/political_communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/political_communication/</guid>
      <description>People do not merely respond to the outside world; they recognize, process, and make choices. I am interested in how this psychological process is achieved within media interactions among the sender, carrier, and receiver. This also makes my research different from the prevalent political-communication studies that focus on the content and means of the media. Instead, I focus more on how people respond to them, for instance, what the audience actually feels, understands, and does when they are exposed to a political message from the government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Political Discourse</title>
      <link>/project/political_discourse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/political_discourse/</guid>
      <description>In studies of official political discourse in non-Western electoral democracies, scholars have focused disproportionately on government discourse itself. Less research explores what happens next.
However, in real politics, the governments often fall into the curse that official discourse is unacceptable, ironic (KUSO), or misused by the public.
I unbox this puzzle by investigating how the public responds to the government officail discourse. Several focused questions include: How do official forms of government discourse (the &amp;ldquo;official voice&amp;rdquo;) spread through different levels of government?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democracy in Modern China</title>
      <link>/project/democracy_in_modern_china/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/democracy_in_modern_china/</guid>
      <description>Socioeconomic inequality includes systematic discrepancies among citizens in income, assets, mobility, accessible resources, etc. I am interested in this structural property&amp;rsquo;s effects, paths, and mechanisms on individual and group political decisions and behaviors. In particular, how do people recognize inequality (what aspects of inequality)? How does their awareness and understanding of inequality affect their political cognition, preferences, and decisions? Even more interestingly, what (or&amp;hellip;who) forms the masses&amp;rsquo; inequality perceptions?
For more imformation, Please visit the project page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SDG localization</title>
      <link>/project/sdg_localization/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/sdg_localization/</guid>
      <description>Language is the fundamental feature of human beings. The debate of whether does language shapes thoughts or the other way around has inspires the greatest theorists and scientists throughout the human history. Nevertheless, the importance of language in political lives has not been well studied yet.
Cutting in from an empirical angle, I strive to identify the influences of linguistic relativity and language planning in the government-mass relationship and the (re)construction of mass political cognition.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
